<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Get Started on</title><link>/docs/get-started/</link><description>Recent content in Get Started on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/docs/get-started/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>🐈 Meet CutieCat</title><link>/docs/get-started/introduction/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Aug 2022 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/get-started/introduction/</guid><description>❤️ If you have a v0 CutieCat, you're an early supporter of the project! Your feedback &amp; suggestions are cherished. What is the CutieCat? # CutieCat is your new hacking &amp;amp; prototyping companion! It&amp;rsquo;s a cat-shaped console that lets you experiment with USB Attacks, Wireless Hacking, and fun mini-projects in CircuitPython.
Our CutieCat add-ons will get you building prototypes in no time!
CutieCat Features # CutieCat is built around the ESP32, a WiFi &amp;amp; Bluetooth capable microcontroller that makes it perfect for low-cost wireless hacks!</description></item><item><title>⚒️ Assembly Guide</title><link>/docs/get-started/assembly/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 00:52:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>/docs/get-started/assembly/</guid><description>⚠️ Updated pics &amp; assembly video coming by Sep 06 2024. ⚙ Parts # Part Description Microcontroller ESP32-S3 WiFi &amp;amp; Bluetooth MCU Screen 128x64px SH1106 OLED Display Pin Header 6 Pin Breakout for CutieCat Add-ons Antenna (Patch) Omni Antenna Antenna (External) Long-range Antenna ℹ️ Learn more about component selection on our hardware guide. 🗒 Steps # 1. Place the ESP32 # a. Melt a tack of solder onto the top right pad.</description></item><item><title>🖥️ Firmware Guide</title><link>/docs/get-started/firmware/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 00:52:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>/docs/get-started/firmware/</guid><description>ℹ️ Our firmware is currently experimental as we continue to explore &amp; make improvements to the DevKitty ecosystem. CutieCat comes flashed with QA Firmware to test basic functionality. To start hacking you&amp;rsquo;ll have to load new firmware. If you&amp;rsquo;re adventurous you can even learn to write your own!
💻 Firmware Guide # ℹ️ Pick a firmware, and keep reading to learn how to flash these projects. Official Firmware # We&amp;rsquo;re constantly adding new features and developing cool hacking tools for the ESP32.</description></item><item><title>👨‍💻 Developer Guide</title><link>/docs/get-started/developer/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 00:52:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>/docs/get-started/developer/</guid><description>ℹ️ This page is under construction. Hardware # Currently not accepting PR&amp;rsquo;s, but fixes &amp;amp; suggestions are welcome!
PCB: Designed in KiCAD Enclosure: Designed in FreeCAD Firmware # ℹ️ Coming soon Tools # ESPTool # ESPTool is the official tool for managing Espressif chips. It can identify boards, modify flash space, and more!
Install ESPTool # pip3 install esptool.py Create a Binary # After developing and writing custom firmware to the ESP32, you may wish to extract a fullsize binary that contains your application, and perhaps files on the flash space.</description></item></channel></rss>