<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>USB Hacking on</title><link>/docs/usb-attacks/</link><description>Recent content in USB Hacking on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/docs/usb-attacks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Introduction</title><link>/docs/usb-attacks/introduction/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Aug 2022 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/usb-attacks/introduction/</guid><description>From time to time, a new exploit in ubiquitous hardware (like USB) is engendered. Taking advantage of such vulnerabilities often requires specialized knowledge, or is patched quickly enough that the attack surface is practically non-existent in real world applications.
However, Keystroke Injection is an exploit that has stood the test of time by taking advantage of a computer&amp;rsquo;s inherent trust of USB Keyboards!
What is Keystroke Injection? # Human Interface Devices (HID) encompass things like mice and keyboards - devices that require practically no setup or authorization to use.</description></item><item><title>ScriptKitty Firmware</title><link>/docs/usb-attacks/scriptkitty-fw/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Nov 2023 19:33:41 -0800</pubDate><guid>/docs/usb-attacks/scriptkitty-fw/</guid><description>ℹ️ Check out the flashing guide to load this firmware on your DevKitty! ScriptKitty is a cat-themed keystroke injection tool that lets you select hundreds of usb attack payloads at the press of a button. You can even deploy attacks remotely via a WiFi interface!
Get the source code and binaries here.
ScriptKitty Introduction # Flash Drive # The ScriptKitty Firmware creates a flash drive when plugged into your computer.</description></item><item><title>Payload Guide</title><link>/docs/usb-attacks/payloads/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 15:21:01 +0200</pubDate><guid>/docs/usb-attacks/payloads/</guid><description>Our ScriptKitty Firmware supports DuckyScript™, making it easy to create your first payload! If you need inspiration, you can find a list of DuckyScrit payloads on the Hak5 GitHub repository.
Payload Methodology # When creating a keystroke injection payload, work backwards! Start by thinking about what you want the payload to accomplish (a RickRoll perhaps), and figure out what programs (web browser, terminal, etc.) have to be launched to achieve that end goal.</description></item><item><title>Config</title><link>/docs/usb-attacks/load-payloads/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 15:21:01 +0200</pubDate><guid>/docs/usb-attacks/load-payloads/</guid><description>To edit the default WiFi network on ScriptKitty, or change the default USB device identifiers on ScriptKitty, you can simply edit the config.txt file on the flash drive! To reload the settings, simply restart your CutieCat!
Settings # Parameter Description Value network WiFi AP SSID anything without spaces password WiFi AP Password must be 8 or more characters vid USB Vendor ID Hex value like 0x00 pid USB Product ID Hex value like 0x00 Emulate USB Devices # By default, the ScriptKitty Firmware emulates an Apple Keyboard to bypass MacOS flagging non-Apple keyboards.</description></item><item><title>Remote Attacks</title><link>/docs/usb-attacks/wifi/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 15:21:01 +0200</pubDate><guid>/docs/usb-attacks/wifi/</guid><description>The ScriptKitty Firmware has a WiFi interface that enables remote access for wireless-triggered USB attacks. Let&amp;rsquo;s try it out!
Connecting # By default, the ScriptKitty firmware uses the following credentials. Just join the access point from your phone or laptop!
Network: DevKitty Password: 12345678 Next, navigate to 192.168.4.1 in a web browser. This brings you to the ScriptKitty attack interface.
Running &amp;amp; Creating Payloads # docs coming soon
Settings # To modify the WiFi credentials, open the config.</description></item><item><title>Live Control API</title><link>/docs/usb-attacks/api/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 15:21:01 +0200</pubDate><guid>/docs/usb-attacks/api/</guid><description>The DevKitty supports live command both through a web interface and via a web API.
Web Interface # To access the web interface and run payloads live, connect to the DevKitty&amp;rsquo;s Wi-Fi access point and visit http://192.168.4.1/create.html
From this page, you can create, run, and save payloads to your DevKitty. Python Script # If you want to use a scrip to send DuckyScript commands or files to your DevKitty, the following scripts will help you get started.</description></item></channel></rss>