<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Setup Guides on</title><link>/docs/guides/</link><description>Recent content in Setup Guides on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/docs/guides/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Assembly Guide</title><link>/docs/guides/dev-kit-assembly/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 00:52:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>/docs/guides/dev-kit-assembly/</guid><description>⚠️ Assembly video &amp; updated pics coming soon. Parts # Buy the DevKitty soldering kit on our webstore!
Part Description Count DevKitty PCB Partially assembled PCB 1 Microcontroller S2 Mini (ESP32-S2 Breakout) 1 Screen SH1106 I2C Display 1 Male Header (Short) S2 Mini Mounting Headers 2 *Female Header (Short) S2 Mini Breakout Headers 2 *Female Header (Long) Expansion Header 1 Learn more about these parts →
Your DevKitty PCB comes with surface mount Buttons, NeoPixel, and Qwiic Connector pre-soldered since these are a little tricky!</description></item><item><title>Firmware Guide</title><link>/docs/guides/pick-firmware/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 00:52:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>/docs/guides/pick-firmware/</guid><description>ℹ️ Our firmware is currently experimental as we continue to explore &amp; make improvements to the DevKitty ecosystem. Overview # The ESP32-S2 is a capable chip that supports WiFi functionality, native USB, and a handful of other nifty features that make it perfect for powering our pocket-sized hacking companions.
At the moment, we&amp;rsquo;re experimenting with custom firmware that maximizes DevKitty&amp;rsquo;s independent strengths - this includes:
DevKitty Wardriver: Cat-themed wardriving &amp;amp; WiFi reconnaissance DevKitty Invader: A simple WiFi attack &amp;amp; network defense tool (coming soon) ScriptKitty: A BadUSB platform with WiFi-triggered attacks &amp;amp; onboard storage!</description></item><item><title>Firmware Update: Browser</title><link>/docs/guides/update-with-chrome/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 15:21:01 +0200</pubDate><guid>/docs/guides/update-with-chrome/</guid><description>ℹ️ WebSerial is an experimental feature that only works in Chrome-based browsers. Step 1: Downloads # Download the Chrome Browser Download the latest DevKitty Firmware Step 2: Place Your DevKitty in Flash Mode # Next, you&amp;rsquo;ll have to place your DevKitty into DFU (Device Firmware Upgrade) mode! You can do this in 2 ways:
Option 1:
Plug the DevKitty into your computer Hold down the 0 button Tap &amp;amp; Release the RST button Option 2:</description></item><item><title>Flashing via Command Line</title><link>/docs/guides/update-with-esptool/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 15:21:01 +0200</pubDate><guid>/docs/guides/update-with-esptool/</guid><description>ℹ️ Unless you hate Chrome, we recommend checking out our browser flashing guide for an easier experience. Step 1: Downloads # Download the latest Firmware Download ESPTool Step 2: Place Your DevKitty in Flash Mode # Next, you&amp;rsquo;ll have to place your DevKitty into DFU (Device Firmware Upgrade) mode! You can do this in 2 ways:
Option 1:
Plug the DevKitty into your computer Hold down the 0 button Tap &amp;amp; Release the RST button Option 2:</description></item></channel></rss>